<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
    <id>nextlibrary</id>
    <name>Knowledge Cards</name>
    <name lang="tr">Bilgi Kartları</name>
    <summary>Knowledge collections with reading progress</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Okuma takipli bilgi koleksiyonları</summary>
    <description><![CDATA[
Knowledge Cards turns your Nextcloud into a small learning library.

Group pages into **collections**, write them with a rich text editor, and let your
team read through them at their own pace. Every page remembers who has read it and
when, so progress is visible at a glance.

- **Collections and pages** — a browsable tree on the left, a reading canvas in the middle, related pages on the right.
- **Reading progress** — mark pages as read; progress bars and badges show what is left.
- **Rich editor** — headings, lists, quotes, code blocks, colours, highlights, callouts, images and video embeds.
- **Roles** — owners and editors write, readers only read. Collections can be public to the instance or private to their members.
- **Trash bin** — deleted collections and pages can be restored.
- **Dark mode** and full-text search across pages.
    ]]></description>
    <description lang="tr"><![CDATA[
Bilgi Kartları, Nextcloud'unuzu küçük bir öğrenme kütüphanesine dönüştürür.

Sayfaları **koleksiyonlar** halinde gruplayın, zengin metin düzenleyiciyle yazın ve
ekibiniz kendi hızında okusun. Her sayfa kimin ne zaman okuduğunu hatırlar; ilerleme
tek bakışta görünür.

- **Koleksiyonlar ve sayfalar** — solda gezilebilir ağaç, ortada okuma kanvası, sağda ilgili sayfalar.
- **Okuma takibi** — sayfaları okundu işaretleyin; ilerleme çubukları ve rozetler kalanı gösterir.
- **Zengin düzenleyici** — başlıklar, listeler, alıntılar, kod blokları, renkler, vurgular, bilgi notları, görseller ve video gömme.
- **Roller** — sahip ve editörler yazar, okuyucular yalnızca okur. Koleksiyonlar sunucuya açık ya da üyelerine özel olabilir.
- **Çöp kutusu** — silinen koleksiyon ve sayfalar geri yüklenebilir.
- **Karanlık mod** ve sayfalarda tam metin arama.
    ]]></description>
    <version>1.0.3</version>
    <licence>agpl</licence>
    <author mail="saficeylan89@gmail.com">Mehmet Safi Ceylan</author>
    <namespace>NextLibrary</namespace>
    <category>organization</category>
    <category>office</category>
    <bugs>https://github.com/SafiCeylan/Nextlibrary/issues</bugs>
    <dependencies>
        <php min-version="8.0" max-version="8.3"/>
        <nextcloud min-version="28" max-version="31"/>
    </dependencies>
    <navigations>
        <navigation>
            <!-- Translated via l10n/*, not a lang attribute: the XSD rejects lang here. -->
            <name>Knowledge Cards</name>
            <route>nextlibrary.page.index</route>
            <icon>app.svg</icon>
            <order>75</order>
        </navigation>
    </navigations>
</info>
